# ANGELO JUNIOR IRAKOZE

# 2nd Level RETAIL IT Support

### CONTACT

+48 729 296 894

irakozangeljunio@gmail.com

# EDUCATION

**PJATK** 

University

2021-PRESENT

IFAK

High School

2013 - 2018

# SKILLS

Soft skills

Linux, ServiceNow, SAP, Citrix and oracle applications such as oracle Sql, Familiar with Java, C++,
Csharp

Interaction skills

Problem solving attidude,

Troubleshooting,

Good communication skills, Goal oriented, MS word and Excel

Linguistic skills

English C1, French C1, German A1

### REFERENCES

Provided upon request.

### SUMMARY

A passionate IT person with over 3 years experience in the field. Known for my hardworking ethic and exceptional people skills. On a daily, I look forward to completing the settled goals by the business within the provided deadline.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### 2ND LEVEL RETAIL IT SUPPORT

Diebold Nixdorf

2024 - Present

Installation of software on devices such as printers and thinclients. We use softwares like citrix ivanti, sql to update database and powershell or cmd to run scripts. Ticketing softwares like oracle based applications and SNOW are used. Management of active directory for admin user modification.

## **IST LEVEL IT SUPPORT**

Diebold Nixdorf

2022 - 2024

Troubleshooting devices with connectivity issues like wifi or ethernet. Software installation and repairing citrix based applications such as Ivanti. Ticketing using oracle based applications and SNOW.

Formation of new agents and refreshing of onboard agents.

### SENIOR 1ST LEVEL IT HELPDESK

Teleperformance Polska

2022

Troubleshooting WIFI and ethernet connections of devices and evaluation of device compliance with requirements. Dispatching technician on site using SNOW. Connecting on devices using citrix based applications in order to resolve incidents.

Monitoring and training new and old 1st level IT helpdesk agents. Implementing new procedures in a general solution database to facilitate troubleshooting.

# 1ST LEVEL IT HELPDESK

Teleperformance Polska

# 2021 - 2022

Troubleshooting WIFI and ethernet connections of devices and evaluation of device compliance with requirements. Dispatching technician on site using SNOW. Connecting on devices using citrix based applications in order to resolve incidents.